Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records UA235
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student Records, 1998 -- 2018; UA235.001; 74.4 Linear Feet
  - Brislin, Lindsay A., 2006; UA235.001.019.0029 (Box 19)
  - Britto, Magdaline, 2006; UA235.001.019.0030; International Student (Box 19)
  - Brown, Benjamin J., 2006; UA235.001.019.0031 (Box 19)
  - Bui, Joseph P., 2006; UA235.001.019.0032 (Box 19)
  - Bui, Son N., 2006; UA235.001.019.0033 (Box 19)
  - Carson, Carly S., 2006; UA235.001.019.0034 (Box 19)
  - Cassidy, Lindsay R., 2006; UA235.001.019.0035 (Box 19)
  - Cha, Yoonil, 2006; UA235.001.019.0036 (Box 19)
  - Chen, Yvonne, 2006; UA235.001.019.0037 (Box 19)
  - Chiang, Wesley M., 2006; UA235.001.019.0038 (Box 19)
  - Chow, Lora L., 2006; UA235.001.019.0039 (Box 19)
  - Churchill, Katherine R., 2006; UA235.001.019.0040 (Box 19)
  - Clark, Matthew J., 2006; UA235.001.019.0041 (Box 19)
  - Clark, Meghan M., 2006; UA235.001.019.0042 (Box 19)
  - Colandrea, Katherine R., 2006; UA235.001.019.0043 (Box 19)
  - Concepcion, Anna M., 2006; UA235.001.019.0044 (Box 19)
  - Cuff, Nicole J., 2006; UA235.001.019.0045 (Box 19)
  - Cunningham, Aimee C., 2006; UA235.001.019.0046 (Box 19)
  - Dawson, Aimee B., 2006; UA235.001.019.0047 (Box 19)
  - Dela Cruz, Roderic L., 2006; UA235.001.019.0048 (Box 19)
  - Desai, Kadam, 2006; UA235.001.019.0049 (Box 19)
  - Dominguez, Cristina C., 2006; UA235.001.019.0050 (Box 19)
  - Doumouras, Michael A., 2006; UA235.001.019.0051 (Box 19)
  - Enright, Sarah M., 2006; UA235.001.019.0052 (Box 19)
  - Fanikos, Laurice S., 2006; UA235.001.019.0053 (Box 19)
  - Feeley, Matthew S., 2006; UA235.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Franco, Elizabeth A., 2006; UA235.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Fulkerson, Brad L., 2006; UA235.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Galarza, Ana M., 2006; UA235.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - Gandhi, Neela, 2006; UA235.001.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - Gerger, Mark A., 2006; UA235.001.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - Go, Sara B., 2006; UA235.001.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - Govostes, John N., 2006; UA235.001.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Griffin, Deborah S., 2006; UA235.001.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Hameed, Asma A., 2006; UA235.001.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - Hansen, Heather D., 2006; UA235.001.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - Harold, David S., 2006; UA235.001.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - Herbert, Jessica S., 2006; UA235.001.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - Ho, Hoa, 2006; UA235.001.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - Hoffman, Jonathan L., 2006; UA235.001.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - Hoskote, Sushma, 2006; UA235.001.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - Howe, Brian J., 2006; UA235.001.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - Hu, Lin, 2006; UA235.001.020.00018 (Box 20)
  - Huang, Yan, 2006; UA235.001.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - Hunton, Anastacia M., 2006; UA235.001.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - Jafry, Fizza A., 2006; UA235.001.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - Jaroonnarm, Jane, 2006; UA235.001.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - Jarquin, Fanny L., 2006; UA235.001.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - Jones, Brant C., 2006; UA235.001.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - Jun, Joon W., 2006; UA235.001.020.00025 (Box 20)
  - Kaddis, Mina J., 2006; UA235.001.020.00026 (Box 20)
  - Karanki, Archanan, 2006; UA235.001.020.00027 (Box 20)
  - Kaur, Harleen, 2006; UA235.001.020.00028 (Box 20)
  - Kahn, Noreen Adnan, 2006; UA235.001.020.00029 (Box 20)
  - Khanbodaghi, Azita, 2006; UA235.001.020.00030 (Box 20)
  - Khedkar, Nina S., 2006; UA235.001.020.00031 (Box 20)
  - Khodush, Anna, 2006; UA235.001.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - Kirk, James E., 2006; UA235.001.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - Kraus, James A., 2006; UA235.001.020.00034 (Box 20)
  - Lee, Jay J., 2006; UA235.001.020.00035 (Box 20)
  - Lee, Joon, 2006; UA235.001.020.00036 (Box 20)
  - Leung, Jason S., 2006; UA235.001.020.00037 (Box 20)
  - Linjawi, Ibtesam A., 2006; UA235.001.020.00038 (Box 20)
  - Lo, Jennifer T., 2006; UA235.001.020.00039 (Box 20)
  - Loukas, Thanasi M., 2006; UA235.001.020.00040 (Box 20)
  - Lubinsky, Craig G., 2006; UA235.001.020.00041 (Box 20)
  - Lucas, Kristin C., 2006; UA235.001.020.00042 (Box 20)
  - Lum, Garrett L., 2006; UA235.001.020.00043 (Box 20)
  - Lum, Julie M., 2006; UA235.001.020.00044 (Box 20)
  - Malhi, Kirandeep K., 2006; UA235.001.020.00045 (Box 20)
  - Manning, Timothy J., 2006; UA235.001.020.00046 (Box 20)
  - Manocha, Viraj, 2006; UA235.001.020.00047 (Box 20)
  - Mayes (Reeves), Amanda, 2006; UA235.001.020.00048 (Box 20)
  - Mellum, Nicholas R., 2006; UA235.001.020.00049 (Box 20)
  - Michel, Stanley, 2006; UA235.001.021.0001 (Box 21)
  - Misner, Rebecca S., 2006; UA235.001.021.0002 (Box 21)
  - Mostowfi, Shiva, 2006; UA235.001.021.0003 (Box 21)
  - Mulroy, Thomas M., 2006; UA235.001.021.0004 (Box 21)
  - Murphy, Katharine A., 2006; UA235.001.021.0005 (Box 21)
  - Muscatiello, Joseph G., 2006; UA235.001.021.0006 (Box 21)
  - Nelson, Justin M., 2006; UA235.001.021.0007 (Box 21)
  - Ng, Edwin Y., 2006; UA235.001.021.0008 (Box 21)
  - Nguyen, Nguyen V., 2006; UA235.001.021.0009 (Box 21)
  - Nguyen, Trinh T., 2006; UA235.001.021.0010 (Box 21)
  - Nielsen, Lisa E., 2006; UA235.001.021.0011 (Box 21)
  - Obianwu, Chilo, 2006; UA235.001.021.0012; International Student (Box 21)
  - Oh, Sandra Z., 2006; UA235.001.021.0013 (Box 21)
  - Oliveira, Kevin L., 2006; UA235.001.021.0014 (Box 21)
  - Olszewski, Teddi A., 2006; UA235.001.021.0015 (Box 21)
  - Osofsky, Joshua T., 2006; UA235.001.021.0016 (Box 21)
  - Osowski, Anne M., 2006; UA235.001.021.0017 (Box 21)
  - Oswald, Christopher S., 2006; UA235.001.021.0018 (Box 21)
  - Pappas, Athena, 2006; UA235.001.021.0019 (Box 21)
  - Park, Sil, 2006; UA235.001.021.0020 (Box 21)
  - Petkevis, Jason R., 2006; UA235.001.021.0021 (Box 21)
  - Pham, Ai-Phuong T., 2006; UA235.001.021.0022 (Box 21)
  - Phan, Uyen N., 2006; UA235.001.021.0023 (Box 21)
  - Prescott, Ashleigh, 2006; UA235.001.021.0024 (Box 21)
  - Prindiville, Brendan D., 2006; UA235.001.021.0025 (Box 21)
  - Purner, Stephanie M., 2006; UA235.001.021.0026 (Box 21)
  - Radovanovic, Yelena, 2006; UA235.001.021.0027 (Box 21)
  - Ravens, Lajuana Calegan, 2006; UA235.001.021.0028 (Box 21)
  - Ravens, Michael A., 2006; UA235.001.021.0029 (Box 21)
  - Ray, Maria L., 2006; UA235.001.021.0030 (Box 21)
  - Richter, Daniel M., 2006; UA235.001.021.0031 (Box 21)
  - Rizkallah, Laura H., 2006; UA235.001.021.0032 (Box 21)
  - Rodrigues, Shannon R., 2006; UA235.001.021.0033 (Box 21)
  - Roghani, Nahid, 2006; UA235.001.021.0034; International Student (Box 21)
  - Rohner, Walter B., 2006; UA235.001.021.0035 (Box 21)
  - Romero, Orlando, 2006; UA235.001.021.0036 (Box 21)
  - Sabari, Shalev S., 2006; UA235.001.021.0037 (Box 21)
  - Samp, Tristi N., 2006; UA235.001.021.0038 (Box 21)
  - Schaeffer, Sarah J., 2006; UA235.001.021.0039 (Box 21)
  - Schweier, Gabriel, 2006; UA235.001.021.0040 (Box 21)
  - Shah, Devang, 2006; UA235.001.021.0041; International Student (Box 21)
  - Shang, Ying M., 2006; UA235.001.021.0042 (Box 21)
  - Shieh, Shihchi, 2006; UA235.001.021.0043 (Box 21)
  - Sin, Donghong, 2006; UA235.001.021.0044 (Box 21)
  - Singla, Rupesh, 2006; UA235.001.021.0045 (Box 21)
  - Smith, Steven D., 2006; UA235.001.021.0046 (Box 21)
  - Sohn, Dae-Jin, 2006; UA235.001.021.0047; International Student (Box 21)
  - Son, Peter I., 2006; UA235.001.021.0048 (Box 21)
  - Stepanchuk, Tatyana I., 2006; UA235.001.021.0049 (Box 21)
  - Suaverdez, Mariacristina Sylvia P., 2006; UA235.001.021.0050 (Box 21)
  - Tarnowski, David S., 2006; UA235.001.021.0051 (Box 21)
  - Tayde, Shital, 2006; UA235.001.021.0052; International Student (Box 21)
  - Tepel, David E., 2006; UA235.001.021.0053 (Box 21)
  - Troung, Loan Le, 2006; UA235.001.021.0054 (Box 21)
  - Ueno, Jeremy K., 2006; UA235.001.021.0055 (Box 21)
  - Valle, Amaury O., 2006; UA235.001.021.0056 (Box 21)
  - Valledor, Gretel, 2006; UA235.001.021.0057 (Box 21)
  - Virani, Nadia, 2006; UA235.001.021.0058 (Box 21)
  - Vrataric, Sofia J., 2006; UA235.001.021.0059 (Box 21)
  - Vuong, Vinh T., 2006; UA235.001.021.0060 (Box 21)
  - Wagner, Cary D., 2006; UA235.001.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - Waltrous, Kevin O., 2006; UA235.001.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Weber, Zachary C., 2006; UA235.001.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Widdison, Joseph J., 2006; UA235.001.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Wood, Daniel E., 2006; UA235.001.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Wu, Ying Jie L., 2006; UA235.001.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - Yoon, Youngjae, 2006; UA235.001.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - Zourdos, Despina Mato, 2006; UA235.001.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - Alva, Aurora R., 2007; UA235.001.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - Anderson, Michelle J., 2007; UA235.001.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - Ardalan, Cyrous, 2007; UA235.001.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - Arruda, Melanie B., 2007; UA235.001.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - Au, Justin J., 2007; UA235.001.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - Backstrom, Amanda K., 2007; UA235.001.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - Baicy, Sarah A., 2007; UA235.001.022.00015 (Box 22)
  - Bajwa, Jagandeep S., 2007; UA235.001.022.00016 (Box 22)
  - Baliga, Narayani, 2007; UA235.001.022.00017 (Box 22)
  - Ballesteros IV, Tomas J., 2007; UA235.001.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - Banga, Pooia, 2007; UA235.001.022.00019 (Box 22)
  - Banga, Sartaj, 2007; UA235.001.022.00020 (Box 22)
  - Barker, Avis L., 2007; UA235.001.022.00021 (Box 22)
  - Batrice, Nassim N., 2007; UA235.001.022.00022 (Box 22)
  - Benchimol, Jacques, 2007; UA235.001.022.00023 (Box 22)
  - Bhupathi Thaker, Shailaja S., 2007; UA235.001.022.00024 (Box 22)
  - Bolduc, Richard C., 2007; UA235.001.022.00025 (Box 22)
  - Boynton, Jonathan C., 2007; UA235.001.022.00026 (Box 22)
  - Bronnberg, Rachel, 2007; UA235.001.022.00027 (Box 22)
  - Buddula, Aravind, 2007; UA235.001.022.00028 (Box 22)
  - Budhani, Aamir, 2007; UA235.001.022.00029 (Box 22)
  - Bui. Minh-Phuong K., 2007; UA235.001.022.00030 (Box 22)
  - Chan, Quinn K., 2007; UA235.001.022.00031 (Box 22)
  - Chang, Zan, 2007; UA235.001.022.00032 (Box 22)
  - Chawla, Seema, 2007; UA235.001.022.00033 (Box 22)
  - Chen, Patricia, 2007; UA235.001.022.00034 (Box 22)
  - Chiu, Nicole P., 2007; UA235.001.022.00035 (Box 22)
  - Choi, Jeong-Yeon, 2007; UA235.001.022.00036 (Box 22)
  - Chua, Shinbei S., 2007; UA235.001.022.00037 (Box 22)
  - Cooper, Michael A., 2007; UA235.001.022.00038 (Box 22)
  - Coppolino, Christina C., 2007; UA235.001.022.00039 (Box 22)
  - Cote, LeeAnn M., 2007; UA235.001.022.00040 (Box 22)
  - Danoukh, Vachik G., 2007; UA235.001.022.00041 (Box 22)
  - Dastjerdi, Diba, 2007; UA235.001.022.00042 (Box 22)
  - Dermawan, Jasmine L, 2007; UA235.001.022.00043 (Box 22)
  - Dhingra, Reema, 2007; UA235.001.022.00044 (Box 22)
  - Fessler, Ian J., 2007; UA235.001.022.00045 (Box 22)
  - Frank, David W., 2007; UA235.001.022.00046 (Box 22)
  - Gabi, Tzur, 2007; UA235.001.022.00047 (Box 22)
  - Gadkar, Viraj, 2007; UA235.001.022.00048 (Box 22)
  - Geller, Jared, 2007; UA235.001.022.00049 (Box 22)
  - Gilmore, Richard D., 2007; UA235.001.022.00050 (Box 22)
  - Goldberg, Jeffrey A., 2007; UA235.001.022.00051 (Box 22)
  - Gonzales, Geoffrey, 2007; UA235.001.022.00052 (Box 22)
  - Goode, Whitney E., 2007; UA235.001.022.00053 (Box 22)
  - Griffee, Justin P., 2007; UA235.001.022.00054 (Box 22)
  - Gundappa, Chitravathi, 2007; UA235.001.022.00055 (Box 22)
  - Haeri, Ashkan, 2007; UA235.001.022.00056 (Box 22)
  - Hallas, Matthew, 2007; UA235.001.022.00057 (Box 22)
  - Hans, Kulvinder, 2007; UA235.001.022.00058 (Box 22)
  - Henville, Jasmin L., 2007; UA235.001.022.00059 (Box 22)
  - Hoffman, Brian P., 2007; UA235.001.022.00060 (Box 22)
  - Hsu, Juliana H., 2007; UA235.001.023.0001 (Box 23)
  - Huang, Lihua, 2007; UA235.001.023.0002; International Student (Box 23)
  - Hyun, Eirleen Y., 2007; UA235.001.023.0003 (Box 23)
  - Jackson, Peter F., 2007; UA235.001.023.0004 (Box 23)
  - Jaffer, Nurin S., 2007; UA235.001.023.0005 (Box 23)
  - Jain, Nidhi, 2007; UA235.001.023.0006; International Student (Box 23)
  - Jarmoc, Marcin, 2007; UA235.001.023.0007 (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Lisa A., 2007; UA235.001.023.0008 (Box 23)
  - Jovic, Vladimir R., 2007; UA235.001.023.0009 (Box 23)
  - Aaronson, Heidi S., 2008; UA235.001.023.0010 (Box 23)
  - Abraham, Pamela, 2008; UA235.001.023.0011 (Box 23)
  - Al-Wazzan, Alaaeddin, 2008; UA235.001.023.0012 (Box 23)
  - Albaugh, Jonathan D., 2008; UA235.001.023.0013 (Box 23)
  - Appelin, Eric C., 2008; UA235.001.023.0014 (Box 23)
  - Armoush, Zeina F., 2008; UA235.001.023.0015 (Box 23)
  - Babo, Nastela, 2008; UA235.001.023.0016 (Box 23)
  - Baptiste, Marjorie, 2008; UA235.001.023.0017 (Box 23)
  - Bedi, Hemjeet, 2008; UA235.001.023.0018 (Box 23)
  - Benson, Julia N., 2008; UA235.001.023.0019 (Box 23)
  - Benton, Patricia A., 2008; UA235.001.023.0020 (Box 23)
  - Blair, Jennifer R., 2008; UA235.001.023.0021 (Box 23)
  - Bliss, Maranda A., 2008; UA235.001.023.0022 (Box 23)
  - Bozarth, Seth H., 2008; UA235.001.023.0023 (Box 23)
  - Brambila, Carmen D., 2008; UA235.001.023.0024 (Box 23)
  - Braunthal, Gonzalo F., 2008; UA235.001.023.0025 (Box 23)
  - Burningham, Tyler, 2008; UA235.001.023.0026 (Box 23)
  - Cabrera, John, 2008; UA235.001.023.0027 (Box 23)
  - Callahan, Daniel M., 2008; UA235.001.023.0028 (Box 23)
  - Cesar, Guimy, 2008; UA235.001.023.0029 (Box 23)
  - Chahal, Sukhman S., 2008; UA235.001.023.0030 (Box 23)
  - Chang, David J., 2008; UA235.001.023.0031 (Box 23)
  - Chao, Jason, 2008; UA235.001.023.0032 (Box 23)
  - Chaudhary, Sanjeet R., 2008; UA235.001.023.0033 (Box 23)
  - Chawla, Sumit, 2008; UA235.001.023.0034 (Box 23)
  - Choi, Eunis, 2008; UA235.001.023.0035 (Box 23)
  - Choi, Janice M., 2008; UA235.001.023.0036 (Box 23)
  - Choi, Keum Kang, 2008; UA235.001.023.0037; International Student (Box 23)
  - Choi, Sun Hae, 2008; UA235.001.023.0038 (Box 23)
  - Chon, Yun H., 2008; UA235.001.023.0039 (Box 23)
  - Christie, Calley J., 2008; UA235.001.023.0040 (Box 23)
  - Chung, Charles, 2008; UA235.001.023.0041 (Box 23)
  - Cockrell, Colby J., 2008; UA235.001.023.0042 (Box 23)
  - Cone, Miles R., 2008; UA235.001.023.0043 (Box 23)
  - Crittendon, Renee W., 2008; UA235.001.023.0044 (Box 23)
  - Delima, Katharina D., 2008; UA235.001.023.0045 (Box 23)
  - Dennison, Melissa M., 2008; UA235.001.023.0046 (Box 23)
  - Dezura, Kelly A., 2008; UA235.001.023.0047 (Box 23)
  - Dinh, Viet T., 2008; UA235.001.023.0048 (Box 23)
  - DiVincenzo, Adam J., 2008; UA235.001.023.0049 (Box 23)
  - Dorosti, Katayoon, 2008; UA235.001.023.0050 (Box 23)
  - Downey, Matthew W., 2008; UA235.001.023.0051 (Box 23)
  - Farrior, Olin, Jr. F., 2008; UA235.001.023.0052 (Box 23)
  - Ferreira, Susan, 2008; UA235.001.023.0053 (Box 23)
  - Gill, Gaganpreet S., 2008; UA235.001.023.0054; International Student (Box 23)
  - Gitangu, Joyce S., 2008; UA235.001.023.0055 (Box 23)
  - Goldman, Winna E., 2008; UA235.001.023.0056 (Box 23)
  - Gomes, Alison, 2008; UA235.001.023.0057 (Box 23)
  - Green, Brian M., 2008; UA235.001.023.0058 (Box 23)
  - Griffith, Kyle R., 2008; UA235.001.023.0059 (Box 23)
  - Gulka, Lauren C., 2008; UA235.001.023.0060 (Box 23)
  - Gunawardena, Dilshan N., 2008; UA235.001.023.0061 (Box 23)
  - Han, Andrew C., 2008; UA235.001.023.0062 (Box 23)
  - Hanson, Lee R., 2008; UA235.001.023.0063 (Box 23)
  - Helley, Christopher P., 2008; UA235.001.023.0064 (Box 23)
  - Hem, Sophana, 2008; UA235.001.023.0065 (Box 23)
  - Henson, Susan E., 2008; UA235.001.023.0066 (Box 23)
  - Hill, Tony P., 2008; UA235.001.023.0067 (Box 23)
  - Hong, Jennifer J., 2008; UA235.001.023.0068 (Box 23)
  - Honig, Amy L., 2008; UA235.001.023.0069 (Box 23)
  - Horan, Matthew J., 2008; UA235.001.023.0070 (Box 23)
  - Hoye, Sarah E., 2008; UA235.001.023.0071 (Box 23)
  - Hua, Ann T., 2008; UA235.001.023.0072 (Box 23)
  - Huang, Kevin, 2008; UA235.001.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Huang, Steve C., 2008; UA235.001.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - Hull, Michael A., 2008; UA235.001.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - Inalou, Sheila, 2008; UA235.001.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - Ishak, Angela, 2008; UA235.001.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - Jayaswal, Neeray, 2008; UA235.001.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - Johnson, Timothy M., 2008; UA235.001.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - Jones, Warren I., 2008; UA235.001.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - Jun, Sookyung, 2008; UA235.001.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - Kang, Jennifer J., 2008; UA235.001.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - Kang, Yoon H., 2008; UA235.001.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - Kapadia, Kanchi, 2008; UA235.001.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - Karabell, Benjamin C., 2008; UA235.001.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - Kavidass, Suveetha, 2008; UA235.001.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - Khaira, Aaron S., 2008; UA235.001.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - Kim, Jin K., 2008; UA235.001.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - Kim, Min Jung, 2008; UA235.001.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - Kumble, Arathi, 2008; UA235.001.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - Laksmana, Theresia, 2008; UA235.001.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - Larsen, Mark A., 2008; UA235.001.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - Larsen, Ryan K., 2008; UA235.001.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - Le, Gregory E., 2008; UA235.001.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - Lee, Dongjin, 2008; UA235.001.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - Lee, Elizabeth G., 2008; UA235.001.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - Lee, John S., 2008; UA235.001.024.00025 (Box 24)
  - Lee, Jung Ho, 2008; UA235.001.024.00026 (Box 24)
  - Lee, Lily C., 2008; UA235.001.024.00027 (Box 24)
  - Leung, Cindy, 2008; UA235.001.024.00028 (Box 24)
  - Liang, Jenny L., 2008; UA235.001.024.00029 (Box 24)
  - Liem, Susan M., 2008; UA235.001.024.00030 (Box 24)
  - Lissauer, Jordan R., 2008; UA235.001.024.00031 (Box 24)
  - Lutskiy, Aleksandr V., 2008; UA235.001.024.00032 (Box 24)
  - Magnuson, Britta E., 2008; UA235.001.024.00033 (Box 24)
  - Maiolo, Claudia E., 2008; UA235.001.024.00034 (Box 24)
  - Marsh, Shawn M., 2008; UA235.001.024.00035 (Box 24)
  - Martin, Joffre J., 2008; UA235.001.024.00036 (Box 24)
  - Martinez, Claudia N., 2008; UA235.001.024.00037 (Box 24)
  - McElligott Faulkner, Lindsey E., 2008; UA235.001.024.00038 (Box 24)
  - Mendez, Zuzana, 2008; UA235.001.024.00039 (Box 24)
  - Miller, Nicholas E., 2008; UA235.001.024.00040 (Box 24)
  - Mitchell, Susannah M., 2008; UA235.001.024.00041 (Box 24)
  - Moheban, Alexander J., 2008; UA235.001.024.00042 (Box 24)
  - Moniz, Teresa S., 2008; UA235.001.024.00043 (Box 24)
  - Montgomery, Marty R., 2008; UA235.001.024.00044 (Box 24)
  - Mower, Matthew S., 2008; UA235.001.024.00045 (Box 24)
  - Murphy, Ryan D., 2008; UA235.001.024.00046 (Box 24)
  - Musicer, Wendy A., 2008; UA235.001.024.00047 (Box 24)
  - Nelms, Stephanie J., 2008; UA235.001.024.00048 (Box 24)
  - Nghiem, Quan M., 2008; UA235.001.024.00049 (Box 24)
  - Noland, Paul B., 2008; UA235.001.024.00050 (Box 24)
  - Nweze, Uchenna L., 2008; UA235.001.024.00051 (Box 24)
  - Pabla, Tarunjeet, 2008; UA235.001.024.00052 (Box 24)
  - Palumbo, Anthony J., 2008; UA235.001.024.00053 (Box 24)
  - Pande, Kanchan, 2008; UA235.001.024.00054 (Box 24)
  - Pang, Allan Y., 2008; UA235.001.024.00055 (Box 24)
  - Park, Jae Yeon, 2008; UA235.001.024.00056 (Box 24)
  - Patel, Bhumi K., 2008; UA235.001.024.00057 (Box 24)
  - Patel, Parita J., 2008; UA235.001.024.00058 (Box 24)
  - Patel, Shivani, 2008; UA235.001.024.00059 (Box 24)
  - Pathak, Aparna, 2008; UA235.001.024.00060 (Box 24)
  - Patoliya, Keyur, 2008; UA235.001.024.00061 (Box 24)
  - Kopacz Peer, Amanda B, 2008; UA235.001.024.00062 (Box 24)
  - Parsi, Lily, 2008; UA235.001.024.00063 (Box 24)
  - Perkins, Nancy L., 2008; UA235.001.024.00064 (Box 24)
  - Pette, Gregory A., 2008; UA235.001.024.00065 (Box 24)
  - Pham, Celine T., 2008; UA235.001.024.00066 (Box 24)
  - Pinkos, Bradford J., 2008; UA235.001.024.00067 (Box 24)
  - Rankin, Kerith E., 2008; UA235.001.024.00068 (Box 24)
  - Ray, Michelle H., 2008; UA235.001.024.00069 (Box 24)
  - Reddy, Bindya, 2008; UA235.001.024.00070 (Box 24)
  - Rezaei, John A., 2008; UA235.001.024.00071 (Box 24)
  - Riebau, Anne T., 2008; UA235.001.024.00072 (Box 24)
  - Rivero, Lorie A, 2008; UA235.001.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Roberts, Michelle K, 2008; UA235.001.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Nanda, Ameeta, 2008; UA235.001.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - Sanam, Vijitha, 2008; UA235.001.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - Sanchez, Joaquin, 2008; UA235.001.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Sandhu, Gurfateh Jang S, 2008; UA235.001.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Sandvi, Christopher G, 2008; UA235.001.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Seppala, Rebecca E, 2008; UA235.001.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - Shaban, Moataz M, 2008; UA235.001.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - Shiva, Ninaz, 2008; UA235.001.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - Singh, Arun Adelphi, 2008; UA235.001.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - Song, Seung-Hee, 2008; UA235.001.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - Stathis, Jeffrey C, 2008; UA235.001.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - Stebbins-Han, Young H, 2008; UA235.001.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - Stipho, Sarah, 2008; UA235.001.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - Stratmeyer, Matthew S, 2008; UA235.001.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - Swing, Timothy C, 2008; UA235.001.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - Tabesh, Leyla, 2008; UA235.001.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - Tantiras, Aphrodite Adelphi, 2008; UA235.001.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - Verbis, Susana Y, 2008; UA235.001.025.00020 (Box 25)
  - Webb, Austin G, 2008; UA235.001.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - Werba, Jordana A, 2008; UA235.001.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - West, Jeffrey C, 2008; UA235.001.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - Wojcicki, Kelly S, 2008; UA235.001.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - Wong, Jade-Lin M, 2008; UA235.001.025.00025 (Box 25)
  - Woods, Jennifer L, 2008; UA235.001.025.00026 (Box 25)
  - Wu, Chuanjun, 2008; UA235.001.025.00027 (Box 25)
  - Yoon, Tae Rim, 2008; UA235.001.025.00028 (Box 25)
  - Yung, Damian, 2008; UA235.001.025.00029 (Box 25)
  - Zaki, Nermine N, 2008; UA235.001.025.00030 (Box 25)
  - Zomorrodian, Sahand, 2008; UA235.001.025.00031 (Box 25)
  - International Class of 2008, UA235.001.025.00032 (Box 25)
  - Abbas, Azher, 2009; UA235.001.025.00033 (Box 25)
  - Albee, Andrew C, 2009; UA235.001.025.00034 (Box 25)
  - Allen, Stephen W, 2009; UA235.001.025.00035 (Box 25)
  - Allison, Michael S, 2009; UA235.001.025.00036 (Box 25)
  - Askari, Marjan, 2009; UA235.001.025.00037 (Box 25)
  - Avsiwala, Tasnim Shabbar, 2009; UA235.001.025.00038 (Box 25)
  - Bartov, Anatoly, 2009; UA235.001.025.00039 (Box 25)
  - Batsevitsky, Bella, 2009; UA235.001.025.00040 (Box 25)
  - Behnoud, Ali, 2009; UA235.001.025.00041 (Box 25)
  - Belden, Amanda G, 2009; UA235.001.025.00042 (Box 25)
  - Benecchi, Jeffrey L, 2009; UA235.001.025.00043 (Box 25)
  - Bienenfeld-Slater, Danielle L, 2009; UA235.001.025.00044 (Box 25)
  - Botezatu, Vlad, 2009; UA235.001.025.00045 (Box 25)
  - Braukus, Erin E, 2009; UA235.001.025.00046 (Box 25)
  - Bui, Quynh Nhu T, 2009; UA235.001.025.00047 (Box 25)
  - Byun, Young Joon, 2009; UA235.001.025.00048 (Box 25)
  - Carey, Joseph F, 2009; UA235.001.025.00049 (Box 25)
  - Carmack, Tyler J, 2009; UA235.001.025.00050 (Box 25)
  - Carraway, Whitney A, 2009; UA235.001.025.00051 (Box 25)
  - Castro, Lauren M, 2009; UA235.001.025.00052 (Box 25)
  - Cervenka, Peter D, 2009; UA235.001.025.00053 (Box 25)
  - Chang, Jae Hee, 2009; UA235.001.025.00054 (Box 25)
  - Ching, Helen H, 2009; UA235.001.025.00055 (Box 25)
  - Choi, Angela J, 2009; UA235.001.025.00056 (Box 25)
  - Chung, Kevin K, 2009; UA235.001.025.00057 (Box 25)
  - Cogliano, John P., 2009; UA235.001.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Conforti, Jason D., 2009; UA235.001.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - Cordero, Franklin A., 2009; UA235.001.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - Coughlin, Corinne A., 2009; UA235.001.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - Daly, Andrew J., 2009; UA235.001.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - Damon, Jeffery R., 2009; UA235.001.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - Dang, John V., 2009; UA235.001.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - Delgado, David A., 2009; UA235.001.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - Delgado, Eunice, 2009; UA235.001.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - Delli Colli, Douglas, 2009; UA235.001.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - Del Mastro, Matthew G., 2009; UA235.001.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - Derisse, Debbie Derisse K., 2009; UA235.001.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - DeWolf, Rebecca L., 2009; UA235.001.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - Dickinson, Richard A., 2009; UA235.001.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - Salam, Furkan, 2009; UA235.001.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - Dogra, Amit, 2009; UA235.001.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - Donelson, David W., 2009; UA235.001.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - Douglas, Allison M., 2009; UA235.001.026.00018 (Box 26)